Kayron Macon

Greater Hartford



kayronmacon@gmail.com



8604782023



linkedin.com/in/kayronmacon

Summary

I am a Responsive Design professional, I have a lot of experience manipulating elements making them 100% responsive on all platforms. I am an experienced UI designer & developer for a startup. My interest in programming is driven by my desire for mathematics and problem-solving.

My area of expertise include:

HTML5, SCSS/CSS3, Javascript, React.js, Python

I have experience designing wireframes with Adobe XD, & Photoshop.

I have mastered making websites responsive, from scratch

Writing concise SCSS, creating mixins & variables that are reusable

Research, design thinking, and developing a pitch deck.

I also have 4 years of sales experience, as well as excellent management & communication skills.

I am currently searching for opportunities that will utilize my current knowledge as well as allow me to grow as a professional.

Github.com/kayronmacon

Portfolio: https://www.kayronmacon.com

Experience



Software Developer

Resource Management Analytics LLC Feb 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months +)



Trainee

Girls For Technology, Inc.

May 2020 - Present (5 months +)

Education



Coursera

Certificate, Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS 2020 - 2020



(A) freeCodeCamp

Responsive Web Design / Javascript Algorithms & Data Structures

Sports and Medical Sciences Academy

Mathematics and Computer Science 2009 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications

- **in** Developing Your Emotional Intelligence LinkedIn
- in Agile Foundations LinkedIn
- Scrum: The Basics LinkedIn
- in Sales Fundamentals LinkedIn
- UX Foundations: Content Strategy LinkedIn

Skills

HTML5 • CSS • CSS Flexbox • JavaScript • React.js • Bootstrap • Responsive Web Design • jQuery • Sales Management • Sales Process